PHEEBS, CAN YOU
HELP ME PICK OUT
AN ENGAGEMENT RING
FOR MONICA?
I CAN'T FIGURE THIS OUT.
IT'S SO HARD.
SHOULD I GET HER A TIFFANY CUT
OR A PRINCESS CUT OR A... OW!
PAPER CUT!
NOW, HAVE YOU TOLD
ANYONE ELSE?
NO. I DON'T WANT
TO TELL ANYBODY ELSE
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
MONICA TO FIND OUT.
YOU TOLD ME.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
I TRUST YOU
AND YOU'RE ONE OF
MY BEST FRIENDS
AND YOU WALKED
IN ON ME
WHILE I WAS LOOKING
AT RING BROCHURES.
YEAH, WELL, ONCE AGAIN,
NOT KNOCKING PAYS OFF.
I ONLY WISH YOU HADN'T
BEEN ON THE TOILET.
ME, TOO.
HEY.
SO, CHANDLER, WANT TO
GO TO THE COFFEE HOUSE?
OH, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, COFFEE HOUSE.
PERFECT. WE WERE JUST GOING
TO SEE IF YOU WANTED TO GO.
OH, WELL, WE DON'T
'CAUSE WE GOT THE OTHER PLACE.
HOW RUDE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
YOU WANT A BITE?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
SO HOW ARE THINGS
GOING WITH PAUL?
GOOD.
ALTHOUGH, YOU KNOW,
HE'S A PRIVATE GUY.
YOU KNOW, I WISH
I COULD GET HIM
TO OPEN UP A LITTLE BIT,
SHARE SOME FEELINGS.
THAT'S EASY.
YOU JUST HAVE TO THINK OF HIM
AS A JAR OF PICKLES
THAT WON'T OPEN.
SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I SHOULD RUN HIM
UNDER SOME HOT WATER
AND BANG HIS HEAD
AGAINST THE TABLE?
NO. THAT'S WHAT YOU DO
WHEN YOU WANT TO GET
THE TRUTH OUT OF SOMEONE.
( chuckles )
HI, HONEY.
HI.
WATCH THIS.
OKAY.
HEY, PAUL.
HI, PHOEBE.
SO, HOW ARE THINGS
GOING WITH YOU?
CAN'T COMPLAIN.
( clucks tongue )
LET'S GO.
OKAY.
HEY!
HI!
ROSS, GOOD
TO SEE YOU, TOO.
HOW YOU DOING?
GOOD. BYE.
OKAY, YOU TAKE CARE.
YEAH!
EW.
HEY, PHEEBS, WHAT WAS THE DEAL
WITH YOU AND CHANDLER
BLOWING US OFF BEFORE?
YEAH, IT WAS SO WEIRD, HUH?
PHOEBE, WHY'D YOU DO IT?
I DIDN'T DO IT.
IT WAS CHANDLER.
HE'S... HE'S MAD AT YOU.
WHA...? WHY?
PLEASE. I THINK YOU KNOW WHY.
CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING.
COME ON, ROSS.
YOU'RE A PALEONTOLOGIST.
DIG A LITTLE DEEPER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS IT 'CAUSE JOEY AND I
DIDN'T INVITE HIM
TO THAT KNICKS GAME
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO?
DO YOU THINK THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT HE'D BE MAD AT YOU FOR?
I GUESS IT COULD.
WELL, THEN, I THINK THAT'S IT.
WELL, IF HE'S ANGRY
HE REALLY SHOULDN'T
JUST COVER IT UP.
I WISH HE WOULD
JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH.
OH, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT
THEN YOU REALLY SHOULD
RUN HIM UNDER HOT WATER
AND BANG HIS HEAD
AGAINST THE TABLE.
HONEY, I MADE A RESERVATION
AT CHINA GARDEN.
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH. NO, THAT'S GREAT.
BUT FIRST, WAIT.
TALK TO ME, TALK TO ME.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR DAY.
IT WAS FINE.
OKAY.
( chuckles )
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING
RIGHT NOW?
I'M THINKING
THAT YOU ARE LOOKING REALLY FINE
IN THAT DRESS.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
GREAT, PAUL
BUT YOU KNOW,
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT...
WOW, THOSE ARE
REALLY GREAT.
UM...
UM, I JUST WANT
TO KNOW WHAT IS
BEHIND THIS STRONG,
SILENT EXTERIOR.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT
STILL WATERS RUN DEEP
AND I WANT TO
SWIM IN YOURS.
ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT HAVING SEX?
NO. PAUL, I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT YOU.
YOU KNOW, LIKE
YOUR CHILDHOOD.
TELL ME ABOUT
NORMAL.
OKAY. WELL, THEN
HOW ABOUT PUBERTY?
COME ON. THAT'S ALWAYS
A PAINFUL TIME.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOUR FRIENDS
INVITE YOU TO A SLUMBER PARTY
AND THEN THEY STICK
YOUR HAND IN WARM WATER
WHILE YOU'RE SLEEPING
SO THAT YOU
PEE IN YOUR
SLEEPING BAG?
NOPE, THAT NEVER
HAPPENED TO ME.
WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY YOU NEVER
MET THAT BITCH SHARON MAJESKI.
ANYWAY, UM,
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU KNOW, ANY REGRETS?
NOPE.
ALL RIGHT, PAUL.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT ASKING
FOR A LOT HERE, OKAY?
JUST GIVE ME SOMETHING.
ANYTHING.
OKAY.
WHEN I WAS SIX YEARS OLD...
MM-HMM.
I WANTED A BIG WHEEL.
AND INSTEAD,
MY PARENTS GOT ME
THIS LITTLE PLASTIC
CHICKEN THAT YOU
HOP AROUND ON.
IT WAS EMBARRASSING.
KIDS MADE FUN OF ME.
OH.
THAT WAS A PRETTY
TOUGH YEAR.
THAT'S GREAT. SEE?
I ALREADY FEEL
LIKE I KNOW YOU
A LITTLE BETTER.
THANK YOU.
OKAY. COME ON.
NOW WE CAN GO EAT.
LET'S GO.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
THEY CALLED ME "CHICKEN BOY."
( sobbing )
AND IN FIFTH GRADE,
I GOT INTO A FIGHT.
WELL, IT WASN'T REALLY A FIGHT.
RICHARD DARUMBULL BIT ME
ON THE NOSE AND I FELL DOWN.
I STILL HAVE A LITTLE SCAR
RIGHT HERE.
YOU CAN SEE IT.
YEAH, I SEE THE SCAR.
LISTEN, PAUL, I THINK
THIS IS REALLY GREAT
THAT, YOU KNOW, YOU'VE
SHARED YOUR FEELINGS.
IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL
BUT, UM, WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE GO SHARE SOME FOOD?
OH, I COULDN'T EAT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU LOVE
THEIR KUNG PAO CHICKEN.
"CHICKEN"?
"CHICKEN BOY!"
I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO DO THIS.
( mimics clucking )
THIS IS THE NINE MILLIONTH
RING STORE WE'VE BEEN TO
AND I CAN'T FIND
THE PERFECT RING.
UGLY RING, UGLY RING,
UGLY RING.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL SELECTION.
OKAY, SO MAYBE YOU
DON'T GET HER A RING.
MAYBE YOU DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
YOU GET HER
AN ENGAGEMENT
BRACELET, YOU KNOW?
OR AN ENGAGEMENT TIARA.
OH, AN ENGAGEMENT
REVOLUTIONARY WAR MUSKET.
YOU KNOW, I'M SO GLAD I PICKED
YOU TO HELP ME WITH THIS.
HUH?
CAN'T YOU JUST IMAGINE
GETTING DOWN ON ONE KNEE
AND HANDING HER THIS
GORGEOUS PIECE OF WEAPONRY?
YEAH, I'M GOING
TO STICK WITH THE RING.
OH, THIS ONE'S NICE.
I LIKE THIS ONE.
SIR, UH, KIND SIR.
CAN I SEE THIS ONE?
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS THE REASON
YOU BROUGHT ME, OKAY?
I KNOW HOW TO HAGGLE
SO LET ME HANDLE THIS
FROM HERE ON OUT.
CAN I HELP YOU?
UH, YES.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE
THAT RING, PLEASE.
OR NOT. WHATEVER.
THIS RING IS
FROM THE 1920s.
IT'S A 1h-CARAT DIAMOND
WITH SAPPHIRES
ON EITHER SIDE.
SIR, COULD I ASK
YOU TO, UM
COULD YOU HOLD OUT THAT RING
AND ASK ME TO MARRY YOU?
OKAY.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
OH, MY GOD. THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE RING.
HOW MUCH IS IT?
CHANDLER,
I WILL HANDLE THIS.
HOW MUCH IS IT?
$8,600.
WE WILL GIVE YOU
TEN DOLLARS.
ARE YOU INTERESTED
IN THIS RING?
YES. YES, BUT I CAN
ONLY PAY $8,000.
OKAY. I CAN LET IT
GO FOR $8,000.
WE STAND FIRM
AT TEN DOLLARS.
HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO PAY?
UH, CREDIT CARD.
OH, NO. BUT I LENT
MY CREDIT CARD TO JOEY.
OKAY, I'LL GO GET IT.
YOU GUARD THE RING.
OKAY.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY
ABOUT BEFORE.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
HERE FOR TEN DOLLARS?
UH, YES.
I HAVE THESE TWO
RATHER BEAUTIFUL
FIVE DOLLAR BILLS.
I'LL GIVE YOU
ONE DOLLAR FOR THEM.
HEY, REMEMBER HOW
CHANDLER AND PHOEBE
BLEW US OFF YESTERDAY?
NO.
REMEMBER? YOU WERE
EATING PIZZA.
YEAH.
OKAY.
WELL, APPARENTLY,
CHANDLER'S ANGRY AT US
FOR NOT GETTING
HIM A TICKET
TO THAT KNICKS GAME
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO JUST GET HIM A TICKET?
THAT GUY IS
ALWAYS MOOCHING OFF OF US.
RIGHT.
ANYWAY, I STILL THINK WE SHOULD
TRY TO PATCH THINGS UP.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, UH...
MAYBE WE CAN GET HIM TICKETS
TO ANOTHER KNICKS GAME
AND INVITE HIM.
OH, WOW, THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA.
AND I STILL HAVE
HIS CREDIT CARD.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
HOLD ON.
I GOT THIS ONE.
HERE YOU GO.
YOU KNOW,
I GOT TO TELL YOU.
SOMETIMES
I DON'T GET CHANDLER.
YOU KNOW, ME AND
HIM DO STUFF
ALL THE TIME WITHOUT YOU
AND YOU DON'T GET
ALL UPSET.
ALL THE TIME?
ALL THE TIME.
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
STILL CRYING?
LIKE A LITTLE GIRL.
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I WANTED HIM TO OPEN UP.
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
I WAS GOING TO UNLEASH
THIS WEEPY, CLINGY,
MOIST MONSTER.
YOU KNOW, I ONLY KNOW
OF TWO SUREFIRE WAYS
TO SHUT A MAN UP
AND ONE OF THEM IS SEX.
WHAT'S THE OTHER ONE?
I DON'T KNOW. I'VE NEVER HAD
TO USE THE OTHER ONE.
I'M JUST SAYING
YOU KNOW, IF WE'RE HAVING SEX,
HE'S NOT GOING TO BE TALKING.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE TALKER.
ANYWAY, UH, GREAT IDEA.
UM, I GOT TO GO TO THE STORE.
I TOLD HIM THAT I WOULD BUY HIM
SOME MORE TISSUES.
OH, WE HAVE SOME HERE.
NO, YOU DON'T!
OKAY. UM, I'D ALSO LIKE
TO TRY ON THE TIARA.
OH, YEAH. OKAY.
WOW. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TOO MUCH?
A TAD.
THEN TAKE THE TIARA BACK
AND LET ME HOLD
THE MUSKET AGAIN.
SOMETHING'S MISSING.
IT'S NOT...
OKAY. OH, LET ME SEE
THE RING
THAT MY FRIEND PICKED OUT.
WHERE'S THE 1920s
PRINCESS-CUT RING?
I JUST SOLD IT
TO THAT GENTLEMAN.
OH, MY GOD!
WAIT! NO!
( alarm blares )
NO! WHAT?! HEY!
LET ME OUT
NOW!
RACHEL?
NO.
HOW ARE YOU, PAUL?
OKAY.
CHANDLER...
DID YOUR DAD EVER HUG YOU?
NO.
DID HE HUG YOU?
NO, I...
IT'S JUST THAT...
MY DAD NEVER DID.
I MISS MY DAD.
WELL, YOU CAN SEE
MY DAD IN VEGAS
KISSING OTHER DADS.
HEY, CHANDLER?
YEAH?
WOULD YOU...
WOULD YOU HUG ME?
I'M A LITTLE BUSY HERE, PAUL.
( crying ):
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
MY DAD USED TO SAY.
OKAY, A QUICK ONE.
COME ON,
HUG IT OUT.
HEY!
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
FIVE MORE SECONDS.
OKAY!
HEY.
JOEY!
WHAT, HEY, WHAT,
HEY, WHAT... HEY.
HI. PAUL, IS IT?
DO YOU HAVE MY CREDIT CARD?
YEAH, IT'S IN MY...
IN... IN MY POCKET.
MY BACK POCKET!
THANK GOD.
HEY, LISTEN, I
GOT US TICKETS
TO A KNICKS
GAME TONIGHT.
OH, I CAN'T GO.
COME ON,
IT'LL BE FUN.
ME, YOU AND ROSS AND...
PAUL, PROBABLY.
Phoebe:
CHANDLER
I FOUND THE PERFECT RING.
OH, THAT'S-THAT'S PRETTY NICE
BUT I'M GOING TO GO
WITH THE ONE I PICKED FIRST.
OH, WAKE UP,
CHANDLER.
THE ONE YOU PICKED IS GONE.
IT'S OVER!
WHAT?
SOME GUY BOUGHT IT.
I'M SORRY.
I TRIED TO STOP IT,
BUT THEY PUT ME IN JAIL.
THEY PUT YOU IN JAIL?
THE LITTLE JAIL
BETWEEN THE DOORS.
PHOEBE, I ASKED YOU
TO GUARD THE RING.
I KNOW--
I'M SORRY...
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THIS RING IS BETTER
AND MONICA NEVER EVEN SAW
THE OTHER RING.
YEAH, BUT WHEN HE PROPOSED
TO ME WITH THE RING
I GOT... GOOSEBUMPS.
MAYBE IT WAS THE GUY.
IT WAS THE RING.
HEY, SO, UH, WAS HE EXCITED
ABOUT THE TICKETS?
NO.
HE BLEW US OFF.
WHAT?
I KNOW!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
CAN I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
I'M A LITTLE MAD
AT HIM NOW.
CAN I TELL
YOU SOMETHING?
ME, TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE DIDN'T WANT TO TALK TO US
ABOUT BEING ANGRY.
WELL, MAYBE WE DON'T TALK
TO HIM AT ALL.
OOH...
FREEZE HIM OUT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I LIKE IT.
EH? WE'LL SHOW HIM.
FROM NOW ON, IT'S GOING
TO BE JOEY AND ROSS--
BEST FRIENDS.
OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO BE THE
NEW JOEY AND CHANDLER.
( door opening )
HI. I'M BACK.
HEY, I HAVE
SO MUCH MORE TO TELL YOU.
I'VE WRITTEN IT ALL DOWN.
AH, THAT'S GREAT.
NO, ACTUALLY, THAT'S...
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S REALLY GREAT.
YOU KNOW, I GOT
TO TELL YOU
WRITING
GETS ME, UH...
GETS ME KIND OF HOT.
WAIT, WAIT, LISTEN.
LISTEN TO THIS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I WANTED
TO BE WHEN I WAS THAT AGE?
A LOVER?
SURFER.
OH, YEAH?
SURFER?
I WANTED TO BE ONE WITH
THE WAVES, YOU KNOW...
OKAY, HONEY,
HOLD ON REAL QUICK.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
LET ME JUST, UH...
GET A LITTLE MORE
COMFORTABLE, HERE.
OH, WAIT. NOW,
WAIT A SECOND.
THIS ISN'T TOO
REVEALING, IS IT?
NO.
"WHATEVER HAPPENED
TO THAT LITTLE DUDE...
SO FULL OF DREAMS?"
I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE LITTLE DUDE!
I CAN'T... I CANNOT
LISTEN TO ANY MORE OF THIS.
THE ONLY PERSON
WHO WOULD WANT TO LISTEN
TO ANY MORE OF THIS
IS A MENTAL HEALTH PROFESSIONAL
AND THAT IS ONLY BECAUSE
THEY GET PAID $100 AN HOUR.
DO YOU MUCH HOW MONEY
I COULD HAVE MADE
LISTENING TO YOU?
$2,000.
AND YOU KNOW
WHEN I FIGURED THAT OUT?
WHILE YOU WERE TALKING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE TRYING
TO STIFLE ME
WHEN JUST 14 HOURS AGO, WE
FIGURED OUT THAT THAT IS EXACTLY
WHAT MY MOTHER WAS TRYING
TO DO TO ME.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I... I... I DON'T MEAN...
DIDN'T MEAN TO STIFLE YOU.
I... THIS IS ALL
JUST A LITTLE OVERWHELMING.
OH, RACHEL.
I'M...
SO SORRY.
OH...
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO OVERWHELM YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT...
WHEN THOSE GATES OPENED
IT WAS HARD TO...
HARD TO CLOSE THEM...
BUT THEY ARE CLOSED NOW,
BELIEVE ME.
I'M SO GLAD.
I'M SO GLAD...
YOU SHARED...
AND I'M GLAD
THAT YOU'RE DONE.
SO WHAT DO YOU
SAY WE, UM...
I'D REALLY LIKE THAT.
MM-HMM.
( moans softly )
( sighs )
THAT WAS...
( crying ):
SO GOOD.
( sobbing )
OH... OH...
YUCK!
HEY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I LET YOU TALK ME
INTO BUYING
THIS STUPID,
GUMBALL-MACHINE-LOOKING RING.
IT'S NOT A STUPID,
GUMBALL-MACHINE-
LOOKING RING.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL RING.
NO, IT'S NOT.
WHEN I LOOKED AT THE OTHER RING
I COULD SEE MONICA'S FACE
WHEN I GAVE IT TO HER,
YOU KNOW?
AND I COULD SEE HER
SAYING, "YES."
WHEN I LOOK AT THIS RING,
ALL I SEE IS A RING...
UNLESS I LOOK AT IT
REALLY CLOSELY
AND THEN...
I CAN SEE MY OWN EYE.
( chuckling )
LOOK, THIS IS
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
I'M GOING TO DO IN MY LIFE.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
IT'S PERFECT.
OKAY, THERE MAY BE A WAY
THAT WE COULD GET
THE OTHER RING BACK
'CAUSE I HEARD
THE GUY TELL THE JEWELER
WHERE HE WAS GOING
TO PROPOSE.
SO, MAYBE WE COULD GET HIM
TO TRADE RINGS OR SOMETHING.
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WELL,
YOU CERTAINLY CAN'T GIVE HER
THAT STUPID
GUMBALL RING.
THERE HE IS.
Chandler:
OKAY, AND HE HASN'T
PROPOSED YET
BECAUSE SHE HAS NO RING
ON HER FINGER.
( gasping ):
WOW, YOU'RE GOOD.
AFTER THIS, WE
SHOULD SOLVE CRIMES.
YEAH.
OKAY, GO-GO-GO GET HIM.
OH, OKAY.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
COULD YOU COME
WITH ME, PLEASE?
YOU HAVE A PHONE CALL.
WHO IS IT?
IT IS YOUR OFFICE.
DO YOU KNOW WHO
AT MY OFFICE?
JOHN.
OH, JOHN. GREAT.
HERE HE IS.
HI, HI.
OKAY, THERE WAS A SLIGHT MIX-UP
AT THE JEWELRY STORE.
THE RING YOU'RE
ABOUT TO PROPOSE WITH
WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE HELD FOR ME.
SO, I'M GOING TO NEED
TO HAVE THAT BACK...
BUT IN EXCHANGE
I'M WILLING
TO TRADE YOU
THIS BEAUTIFUL,
MORE EXPENSIVE RING.
WOW.
I WOULD TRADE.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL
BUT I'M GOING TO
USE THIS ONE.
NOW, IF YOU'LL
EXCUSE ME.
NO, NO, SEE,
THIS IS MY FIANCEE
AND HER HEART WAS SET
ON THAT RING.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO BREAK HER HEART, NOW, DO YOU?
YEAH, DO YOU WANT
TO BREAK A DYING WOMAN'S HEART?
YOU'RE DYING?
( coughing )
YES, SHE'S DYING...
OF A COUGH, APPARENTLY.
Phoebe:
YES...
AND IT IS MY DYING WISH
TO HAVE THAT RING.
SEE, IF I'M NOT
BURIED WITH THAT RING
THEN MY SPIRIT IS GOING
TO WANDER THE NETHERWORLD
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH,
HONEY.
UH... I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME SEE THE RING.
GREAT.
OKAY, HERE.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL DO IT.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, AND YOU ARE
ABOUT TO MARRY A WONDERFUL MAN.
HEY, I'M MARRYING
A DEAD WOMAN.
Announcer:
Rebound, Ronaldson again.
Remember, Jamal Falkner was...
GUYS...
( game continuing )
The ball is blocked by Hendren.
I GOT SOMETHING IMPORTANT
TO TELL YOU.
GUYS?
...get up in the air.
Dent made a nice move.
GUYS?
Watch Mario Bennett, now.
He's going
to take a nice sweep...
I'M GOING TO ASK MONICA
TO MARRY ME.
( TV stops playing )
I THINK WE GOT
TO END THE FREEZE-OUT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS TH... IS THIS FOR REAL?
YEAH.
CHECK OUT THE RING.
OH, MY GOD!
SO, YOU TWO ARE
REALLY SERIOUS?
YEP, PRETTY MUCH.
Y-YOU'RE GOING
TO GET MARRIED?
I MEAN... WE'RE GOING
TO BE BROTHERS-IN-LAW.
COME HERE.
( laughing )
A-A-A-A-A-AND-AND WE'RE GOING
TO BE FRIENDS AGAIN.
HEY...
WHAT?
WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE.
OKAY.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
I WAS GOING TO WAIT TILL, UH,
IT WAS OFFICIAL, YOU KNOW
BUT I GOT SO EXCITED
I JUST HAD TO TELL YOU GUYS
'CAUSE YOU'RE MY BEST FRIENDS.
I THINK I'M GOING
TO CRY.
OH, NO MORE CRYING... PLEASE.
I JUST DUMPED ONE CRYBABY.
I'LL DUMP YOU, TOO.
GO, GO, GO, GO.
I'M GOING TO ASK MONICA
TO MARRY ME.
OH, MY GOD.
( gasping )
OH, CHANDLER!
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO BE SO HAPPY.
I KNOW.
( crying ):
WHERE'S ALL THE TISSUE?
CHECK OUT THE RING.
OH!
NICE. 1h CARAT, EASY.
HEY.
Ross:
CHANDLER'S GOING
TO ASK MONICA
TO MARRY HIM.
OH, I KNOW. I HELPED
PICK OUT THE RING.
OH...
YOU TOLD HER
BEFORE YOU TOLD US?
WELL, SHE WALKED IN
WHILE I WAS LOOKING
AT THE RING BROCHURES.
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
THAT, RIGHT?
GUYS?